A Guide to the Papers of Howard W. Smith, 1933-1966
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series IX: National Labor Relations Board Files
  - Article by Judge Smith, Christian Science Monitor, April 27, 1940 (Box 220)
  - Speech in New York [Chamber of Commerce of Queens, 28 April 1941] (Box 221)
  - Responses to Final Report (Box 221)
  - National Labor Relations Resolution - 76th Congress (Box 221)
  - To Be Investigated N.L.R.B. - 2-27/40 (Box 221)
  - Personnel (Box 221)
  - Opposed to Amendments (Box 221)
  - Saposs - (also his division of N.L.R.B.) (Box 221)
  - News Releases (Box 221)
  - Speech delivered to Maryland State Bar Association [29 June 1940] (Box 221)
  - [Requests for copy of report on N.L.R.B.] (Box 221)
  - Memorandae to and from Mr. Toland (Box 221)
  - News article by Charles A. Wood (Box 221)
  - Printing (Box 221)
  - Printing of Report (Box 221)
  - John Stoddard - correspondence re committee (Box 221)
  - Reporting of Hearings (Box 221)
  - Requests for Hearings When and If Printed (Box 221)
  - Mailed Reports To (Box 222)
  - Speech, 18 December 1939 - Star Radio Forum; on N.L.R.B. (Box 222)
  - Miscellaneous (2 folders) (Box 222)
  - Personnel - Investigations - Counsel - Applicants (Box 223)
  - [Cases? - folders A-D; E-L; M-S; T-Z] (Box 223)
  - Personnel Data (Box 223)
  - [Personnel Application Forms - folders A-F] (Box 223)
  - [Personnel Application Forms - folders G-L; M-R; S-Z] (Box 224)
  - Committee Selection of Personnel (Box 224)
  - Requests for Copies of Hearings [Proceedings] (Box 225)
  - To be filed [request for copies of Hearings] (Box 225)
  - N.L.R.B. [printed bills, etc.] (Box 225)
  - Clippings on the Smith Committee to Investigate the N.L.R.B.: 21 December 1940 - 11 January 1941 [scrapbook] (Box 225)
  - N.L.R.B. Housekeeping Records, 1939-40 (Box 226)
  - Financial ledger of committee (Box 226)
  - Bills, vouchers, letters, etc. (5 folders) (Box 226)
  - Travel & expenses of committee members (Box 227)
  - Fees & expenses of witnesses (Box 227)
  - Telephone & Telegraph charges (Box 227)
  - Contracts - Rentals (office furniture) (Box 227)
  - Copies of all vouchers (Box 227)
  - Uncollected bundle of vouchers (Box 227)
  - Multilithing; mimeographing; printing; photostating, etc. (Box 227)
  - Office and stationery supplies (Box 228)
  - Cont. list of all vouchers (Box 228)
  - Pay roll (Box 228)
  - Rental expenses (Box 228)
  - Miscellaneous expenses (Box 228)
  - Travel expenses (Box 229)
  - Special stenographers, typing & clerical expenses Due bills (Box 229)
  - Forms, pink supoena (Box 229)
  - Extra copies of telegrams (Box 229)
  - Appointments (Box 229)
  - Receipts (Box 229)
  - Expense accounts (Box 229)
  - Inventory: Requisitions & charge tickets (Box 229)
  - Travel (confirmations) (Box 229)
- Series X: Strasbourg Conference Records
  - Official Reports and Proceedings of Strasbourg Conference between U.S. and Council of Europe, November 19-23, 1951 (Box 230)
  - Official Record of Delegates (Box 230)
  - Itinerary of U.S. Delegation (Box 230)
  - Biographical notes on European representatives (Box 230)
  - Speech of Paul Reynaud (Box 230)
  - Official Reports: Nov. 19, p.m.; Nov. 20, a.m.; Nov. 20, p.m.; Nov. 21, a.m.; Nov. 21, p.m.; Nov. 22, a.m.; Nov. 22, p.m.; Nov. 23, a.m.; Nov. 23, p.m. (Box 230)
  - Official Dorr-statement on Marshall Plan and Turkey (Box 230)
  - American Delegation Closing Statement, Nov. 23, 1951 (Box 230)
  - Speeches: 1) Mr. Glenvil Hall (Box 230)
  - Speeches: 2) M. Guy Mollet (Box 230)
  - Documents and Items re: Strasbourg Conference
    - Committee Reprint: Basic Information on Implementation of the North Atlantic Treaty, Feb. 15, 1951 (Box 231)
    - Committee on Foreign Relations: North Atlantic Treaty Exec. Report No. 8, 1949 (Box 231)
    - Committee on Foreign Affairs: Mutual Defense Assistance Act of 1949 as Amended, Oct 2, 1950 (Box 231)
    - Committee on Foreign Affairs: Economic Cooperation Act of 1948, as amended, Aug. 4, 1950
    - Exec. L. - Message of President on North Atlantic Treaty, April 1949 (Box 231)
    - Strasbourg Delegation Report, Sen. Theodore F. Green - The Union of Europe; Its Progress, Problems, Prospects, and Place in the Western World. Doc. No. 90, Jan. 21, 1950 (Box 231)
    - Foreign Relations Committee - North Atlantic Treaty (document relating to), Doc. No. 48, April 12, 1949 (Box 231)
    - H.R. 5113 - Public Law 165 - 82nd Congress - Act to maintain secuirty and promote foreign policy and provide assistance to friendly nations (Box 231)
    - S. Con. Res. 36 - 82nd Congress, 1st Session - to send delegation to Strasbourg (Box 231)
  - Miscellaneous Items
    - Itinerary to Strasbourg Council of Europe (Box 231)
    - Memorandum re: travel arrangements (Box 231)
    - Secuirty facts (Box 231)
    - Committee on General Affairs, Oct. 12, 1955 (Box 231)
    - Address by Joseph P. Kennedy - "Our Foreign Policy, Its Casualties and Prospects", Dec. 17, 1951 (Box 231)
    - R.W.G. MacKay - Heads in the Sand, Oxford: Blackwell, 1950 (Box 231)
    - Copy - Draft Treaty Embodying the Statute of the European Community, Paris, 1952-53 (Box 231)
    - Council of Europe - Statute of the Council of Europe and Rules of Procedure of the Consultiative Assembly Strasbourg, 1951 (Box 231)
    - United Nations - The Impact of the Universal Declaration of Human Rights (Box 231)
    - Office of High Commission for Austria - Allied Commission for Austria: A Handbook (Box 231)
    - Organization for European Economic Cooperation- European Economic Cooperation, Vol. I & II (Box 231)
    - Fred L. Schuman, "The Council of Europe" - reprint, The American Political Science Review, Vol. XLV, No. 3, Sept. 1951 (Box 231)
    - MacKay, M. B. et al., Special Report - Consultative Assembly, Oct. 16, 1951 (Box 231)
    - Council of Europe - The Union of Europe. Its Progress, Problems, Prospects, and Place in Western World, Strasbourg, Oct. 1951. (Box 231)
    - United Nations - Activities of Committee on Human Rights, March 1951 (Box 231)
      seating charts, reports, etc.
    - Folder - "Mr. Smith goes to Europe" (Box 231)
- Series XI: Post Office Correspondence
  - Miscellaneous Files (Box 232)
  - Acorn (Westmoreland County) (Box 232)
  - Aldie Postmastership (Box 232)
  - Alexandria (Box 232)
  - Alfonso (Box 232)
  - Alps (Box 232)
  - Arcola (Box 232)
  - Ashburn (Box 232)
  - Ashland (Box 232)
  - Aylett (Box 232)
  - Balty (Box 232)
  - Barboursville (Box 232)
  - Batesville (Albemarle County) (Box 232)
  - Bealeton (Box 232)
  - Beaverdam (Box 233)
  - Belmont (Box 233)
  - Beverlyville (Box 233)
  - Bluemont Postmastership (Box 233)
  - Boston (Culpeper County) (Box 233)
  - Bowling Green (Box 233)
  - Brandy (Box 233)
  - Bristow (Box 233)
  - Broad Run (Box 233)
  - Brooke (Box 233)
  - Bremo Bluff (Box 233)
  - Browns Store (Box 234)
  - Burgess (Box 234)
  - Bumpass (Box 234)
  - Burr Hill (Box 234)
  - By-bee (Box 234)
  - Callao (Box 234)
  - Calverton (Box 234)
  - Cardwell (Box 234)
  - Carysbrook (Box 234)
  - Casanova (Box 234)
  - Catlett (Box 234)
  - Catharpin (Box 234)
  - Cismont (Box 234)
  - Cobham (Box 234)
  - Cohasset (Box 234)
  - Charlottesville (Box 235)
  - Coles Point (Box 235)
  - Colonial Beach (Box 235)
  - Columbia Route #1 (Fluvanna County) (Box 235)
  - Corbin (Box 235)
  - Culpeper (Box 235)
  - Crozet (Box 235)
  - Dahlgren (Box 235)
  - Dabneys (Louisa County) (Box 235)
  - Delaplane (Box 236)
  - Ditchley (Box 236)
  - Dogue (Box 236)
  - Doswell (Box 236)
  - Downings (Box 236)
  - Dumfries (Box 236)
  - Dyke (Box 236)
  - Earlysville (Box 236)
  - Edgehill (Box 236)
  - Edwardsville (Box 236)
  - Elkwood (Box 236)
  - Ellerson (Box 236)
  - Emmerton (Box 236)
  - Esmont (Box 236)
  - Fairport (Box 237)
  - Falmout (Box 237)
  - Farnham (Box 237)
  - Ferncliff (Box 237)
  - Fife (Box 237)
  - Foneswood (Box 237)
  - Fork Union (Box 237)
  - Foxwells (Box 237)
  - Fredericksburg (Box 237)
  - Frederick Hall (Box 238)
  - Free Union (Box 238)
  - Gainesville (Box 239)
  - Garrisonville (Box 239)
  - Geer (Greene County) (Box 239)
  - Gether (Box 239)
  - Glen Allen (2 folders) (Box 239)
  - Goby (Box 239)
  - Goldvein (Box 239)
  - Gonyon (Box 239)
  - Goochland (Box 239)
  - Gordonsville (Box 239)
  - Grosslands (Box 239)
  - Greenwood (Box 239)
  - Gum Springs (Box 239)
  - Hadensville (Box 239)
  - Hague (Box 239)
  - Hamilton (Box 239)
  - Hanover (Box 239)
  - Hartwood (Box 240)
  - Hatton (Box 240)
  - Haymarket (Box 240)
  - Haynesville (Box 240)
  - Heards (Box 240)
  - Heathsville (Box 240)
  - hewlett (Box 240)
  - Hinnon (Box 240)
  - Howardsville (Box 240)
  - Hume (Box 240)
  - Hyacinth (Box 240)
  - Hylos (Box 240)
  - Index (Box 240)
  - Irvinton (Box 240)
  - Irwin (Box 240)
  - Ivy Depot (Box 240)
  - Jefferson Rural Route (Box 240)
  - Jersey (Box 240)
  - Keene (Box 240)
  - Kents Store (Box 240)
  - Keswick (Box 240)
  - Kilmarnock (Box 241)
  - King George (Box 241)
  - King William (Box 241)
  - Kinsale (Box 241)
  - Lancaster (Box 241)
  - Leesburgh (Box 241)
  - Ladysmith (Box 241)
  - La Rore (Box 241)
  - Lanesville (Box 241)
  - Lewisette (Box 241)
  - Lilian (Box 241)
  - Lincoln (Box 241)
  - Litwalton (Box 241)
  - Lively (Box 241)
  - Locust Grove (Box 242)
  - Lorne (Box 242)
  - Lottsburg (Box 242)
  - Louisa (Box 242)
  - Lovettsville (Box 242)
  - Lucketts (Box 242)
  - Maidens (Box 242)
  - Manassas (Box 242)
  - Manakin (Box 242)
  - Maple Grove (Box 242)
  - Marshall (Box 242)
  - Mongohick (Box 243)
  - Markham (Box 243)
  - Manquin (Box 243)
  - Mechanicsville (Box 243)
  - Merry Point (Box 243)
  - Midway Island Swellings (Box 243)
  - Milford (Box 243)
  - Middleburg (Box 243)
  - Midland (Box 243)
  - Miller School (Box 243)
  - Mine Run (Box 244)
  - Millenbeck (Box 244)
  - Mineral (Box 244)
  - Miskimon (Box 244)
  - Mission Home (Box 244)
  - Mitchells (Box 244)
  - Mollusk (Box 244)
  - Montepelier (Box 244)
  - Montpelier Station (Box 244)
  - Montross (Box 244)
  - Morattico (Box 244)
  - Mount Holly (Box 244)
  - Nindes Store (Box 245)
  - Nokesville (Box 245)
  - Noel (Box 245)
  - Nomini Grove (Box 245)
  - North Garden (Box 245)
  - Nuttsville (Box 245)
  - Oak Grove (Box 245)
  - Occoquan (Box 245)
  - Oilville (Box 245)
  - Oldham (Box 245)
  - Ophelia (Box 245)
  - Orange (Box 245)
  - Orlean (Box 245)
  - Ottoman (Box 245)
  - Owens (Box 245)
  - Paeonian Springs (Box 246)
  - Palmer (Box 246)
  - Palmyra (Box 246)
  - Paris (Box 246)
  - Partlow (Box 246)
  - Pemberton (Box 246)
  - Philmont (Box 246)
  - The Plains (Box 246)
  - Port Royal (Box 246)
  - Purcellville (Box 246)
  - Quinque (Box 246)
  - Quantico (Box 246)
  - Rapidan (Box 247)
  - Rappanhannock (Box 247)
  - Rectortown (Box 247)
  - Reedsville (Box 247)
  - Regina (Box 247)
  - Remington (Box 247)
  - Reva Route (Box 247)
  - Rhoadsville (Box 247)
  - Richardsville (Box 247)
  - Rixeyville (Box 248)
  - Robley (Box 248)
  - Rock Castle (Box 248)
  - Rockville (Box 248)
  - Rollins Fork (Box 248)
  - Round Hill (Box 248)
  - Ruby (Box 248)
  - Ruckersville (Box 248)
  - Ruther Glen (Box 248)
  - Sandy Hook (Box 248)
  - Scottsville (Box 248)
  - Sealston (Box 248)
  - Shiloh (Box 248)
  - Sharps (Box 248)
  - Shadwell (Box 248)
  - Shumansville (Box 248)
  - Snell (Box 248)
  - Somerset (Box 249)
  - Somerville (Box 249)
  - Spotsylvania (Box 249)
  - Standardsville (Box 249)
  - Stafford (Box 249)
  - State Farm (Box 249)
  - Sterling (Box 249)
  - Rural Route - Stevensburg (Box 249)
  - Stratford (Box 249)
  - Sumerduck (Box 249)
  - sunnybank (Box 249)
  - Sweet Hall (Box 249)
  - Templeman (Box 250)
  - Tetotum (Box 250)
  - Thornburg (Box 250)
  - Tidewater (Box 250)
  - Trvilians (Box 250)
  - Triangle (Box 250)
  - Troy (Box 250)
  - Unionville (Box 250)
  - Upperville (Box 250)
  - Vienna (Box 250)
  - Vint Hill (Box 250)
  - Villiage (Box 250)
  - Walmsley (Box 250)
  - Warrenton (Box 250)
  - Warsaw (Box 251)
  - Washington's Birthplace (Box 251)
  - Waterford (Box 251)
  - Weems (Box 251)
  - Westmoreland (Box 251)
  - West Point (Box 251)
  - Wiscomico Church (Box 251)
  - White Hall (Box 251)
  - White Stone (Box 251)
  - Woodbridge (Box 251)
  - Woodford (Box 251)
  - Zacata (Box 251)
  - Post Office Material, 1930's, 1940's, 1950's
    - Manassas (Box 252)
    - Scottsville (Box 252)
    - Beaverdam (Box 252)
    - Louisa (Box 252)
    - Culpeper (Box 253)
    - Esmont (Box 253)
    - Parker (Box 253)
    - Campbell (Box 253)
    - Widewater (Box 253)
    - Lerty (Box 253)
    - Brockenburg (Box 253)
    - Brockroad (Box 253)
    - Horners (Box 253)
    - Luttrellville (Box 254)
    - Mila (Box 254)
    - Madison Run (Box 254)
    - Post Oak (Box 254)
    - Pendleton (Box 254)
    - Potomac Mills (Box 254)
    - Avalon (Box 254)
    - Monaskon (Box 254)
    - Golddale (Box 254)
    - Chiltons (Box 254)
    - Ethel (Box 254)
    - Mulch (Box 254)
    - Boyd Tavern (Box 254)
    - Brook Vale (Box 254)
    - Morrisville (Box 254)
    - Wildwood (Box 254)
    - Horse Head (Box 254)
    - Byrdton (Box 254)
    - Eheart (Box 254)
    - Chestnut Hill (Box 254)
    - Stoney Point (Box 254)
    - Saint George (Box 254)
- Series XII: Service Academies Correspondence
  - West Point 1945 (Box 255)
  - Annapolis (Box 255)
  - Navy 1946 (Box 255)
  - West Point 1946 (Box 255)
  - Annapolis 1946 (Box 255)
  - Annapolis 1946, J-Y (Box 256)
  - West Point 1947 (Box 256)
  - Annapolis 1947 (Box 256)
  - Naval Academy 1948 (Box 256)
  - West Point 1948 (Box 256)
  - West Point 1949 (Box 256)
  - Naval Academy 1949 (Box 256)
  - U.S. Naval Academy 1950 (Box 257)
  - U.S. Military Academy 1950 (Box 257)
  - U.S. Naval Academy 1951 (Box 257)
  - Naval Academy 1951 (Box 257)
  - U.S. Military Academy 1951 (Box 257)
  - Naval Academy, Class of 1952 (Box 257)
  - Military Academy, Class of 1952 (Box 257)
  - Naval Academy, Class entering in 1953 (Box 258)
  - Candidates from 10th District for class entering 1953 (Box 258)
  - Naval Academy 1954 (Box 258)
  - Military Academy, Class entering in 1953 (Box 258)
  - U.S. Military Academy, Class entering in 1953 (Special examination held March 23, 1953) (Box 258)
  - Military Academy 1954 (Box 258)
  - Applicants for admission to service schools, 10th District (Box 258)
  - Misc. Naval & Military Academy 1957 (Box 259)
  - Military and Naval Academy, Classes entering in 1956 (Box 259)
  - Naval Academy, Class entering in 1955 (Box 259)
  - Military Academy, Class entering in 1955 (Box 259)
  - Air Force Academy (01d) (Box 260)
  - Air Force Academy 1957 (Box 260)
  - Air Force Academy 1958-1959 (Box 260)
  - Military and Naval Academy, For Class of 1958 (Box 260)
  - Academies - for 1960 vacancy (Box 260)
  - Academies - for 1960 vacancy (Box 261)
  - U.S. Air Force Academy 1961 (Box 261)
  - U.S. Air force Academy 1962 (Box 261)
  - Academies - for 1962 vacancy (Box 261)
  - Military & Naval Academy. For Class entering 1957 & 1958 (Box 262)
  - Academies 1963 (Box 262)
  - Air Force Academy 1963 (Box 262)
  - Academies 1964 (Box 262)
  - Air Force Academy 1964 (Box 263)
  - Air Force Academy 1965 (Box 263)
  - Military & Naval Academy 1965 (Box 263)
  - Military & Naval Academy 1966 (Box 263)
  - Air Force Academy 1966 (Box 264)
  - U.S. Coast Guard Academy (Box 264)
  - U.S. Merchant Marine Academy (Box 264)
- Series XIII: Thomas Jefferson Memorial Commission Records
  - Thomas Jefferson Memorial Commission (3 folders) (Box 265)
  - Misc. proposal for Thomas Jefferson Memorial (Box 266)
  - To be taken up at next meeting (folder) (Box 266)
  - Thomas Jefferson Papers (Box 266)
  - Papers of Thomas Jefferson, The Letters, writings, etc. (Box 266)
  - Thomas Jefferson Memorial Dedication (Box 266)
  - Pamphlet-Patriotic Pilgrimage re: Virginia Historic sites (Box 266)
  - Folder of minutes of Thomas Jefferson Memorial Commission meetings (Box 267)
  - Specifications for Memorial (Box 267)
  - H.R. 4 sets of blueprints (Box 267)
  - Thomas Jefferson File - miscellaneous correspondence, received during 79th Congress (Box 268)
  - Jefferson Memorial (2 folders) (Box 268)
  - Thomas Jefferson Memorial file beginning Oct. 12, 1938 (Box 268)
  - Untitled folder (Box 268)
  - Thomas Jefferson Memorial Commission - Sculpture (Box 268)
  - Meetings of Commission (Box 268)
  - Miscellaneous items - Thomas Jefferson Memorial Commission (Box 269)
    16 sets of blueprints
  - H.R. 1 set of architectural plans (Box 270)
  - Miscellaneous construction plans, bidders, regulations, etc, letters (Box 270)
  - H.R. 2 reports of Thomas Jefferson Memorial Commission (Box 270)
- Series XIV: Miscellaneous Files
  - Personal Office payroll Account, September 1939 - July 1, 1940 (Box 271)
  - Personal Office payroll Account, September 1939 (Box 271)
  - Loose-leaf office supply book, December 1939-July, 1940 (Box 271)
  - Annotated National Science Foundation, 12th Annual Report, 1962 (Box 271)
  - Va. State Democratic Party. Democratic Party Plans: Plan of Organization..., Richmond: June 9, 1932 (4 copies) (Box 271)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia. Votes Cast...General Election, Nov. 8, 1949, Richmond: 1949 (2 copies) (Box 271)
  - Army Engineers Report re: Seneca Dam Project (Box 271)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia. Soil and Water Conservation, Richmond: Social Conservation Service, 1965 (Box 271)
  - Loose-leaf pamphlet - Soil and Water Conservation Planning in Virginia (Box 272)
  - U.S. Army Engineers Division, U.S. Army Corps of Engineers. Water Resources Development: Virginia, 1965 (Box 272)
  - U.S. Department of Interior. Potomac Weekly (preliminary report on landscape and recreation), May, 1966 (Box 272)
  - Map - Fairfax County, Va. Property I.D. april 1, 1965 (Box 272)
  - Map - Fairfax County, Va. Voting Precincts, 1965 (Box 272)
  - Reprint - The Richmond News Leader, June 30, 1966, endorsing Judge Smith (Box 272)
  - Pictorial Guide of U.S. Capitol (Box 272)
  - Pictorial Story: The Capitol, Symbol of Freedom (Box 272)
  - Ford Foundation - Annual Report, 1956 (Box 272)
  - Ford Foundation - Annual Report, 1960 (Box 272)
  - Magazine and Newspaper article re: Judge Smith (Box 273)
  - "Big Wheels of Washington", Look, April 26, 1960 (Box 273)
  - "The House Rules Committee...Life or Death?", Nation's Agriculture, Dec. 1960 (2 copies) (Box 273)
  - "Chairmen Says; Rules Committee Helps You", Nation's Business, Jan. 1961 (Box 273)
  - "The Enemy Within Our Gates", reporduction from The National Republic, Aug. 1940 (3 copies) (Box 273)
  - Raymond Moley, "Smith of Virginia", Newsweek, Aug. 25, 1958 (2 copies) (Box 273)
  - The Commonwealth, Nov. 1953 (2 copies) (Box 273)
  - Virginia Walter Davis, "Howard W. Smith of Virginia", The Commonwealth, Aug. 1955 (Box 273)
  - Virginia Walter Davis, "Star Performer on 'The Hill'", Virginia Record, May 1957 (2 copies) (Box 273)
  - Labor, Feb. 9, 1963 (Box 273)
  - Loudoun Times-Mirrow, Nov. 16, 1961, (Civil War Commemoration) (Box 273)
  - The Chronicle, July 22, 1938 - Red Scare (Box 273)
  - Investor America, May 1940 re: Labor Acts (Box 273)
  - The United States News, March 1, 1940 re: N.L.R.B. (Box 273)
  - The Arlington Chronicle, July 22, 1938 re: Communists (Box 273)
  - The Commonwealth Monitor, July 30, 1938, "Smith Blasts Opponents" (Box 273)
  - Edward R. Sneed - How Far Down the Road? Conservative comments (Box 273)
  - American Bar Association Journal, January 1942 (Box 273)
  - Look Magazine, April 26, 1960 (Box 273)
  - Newsweek, Aug. 25, 1958 (Box 273)
  - Roll Call, July 12, 1956 (Box 273)
  - Time, Feb. 2, 1959 (Box 273)
  - Time, Sept. 5, 1959 (Box 273)
  - Time, July 21, 1961 (Box 273)
  - Campaign flyer, 1950 (Box 273)
  - Personal sketches (13) (Box 273)
  - Senate Document 13 - Our Capitol (Box 274)
  - Library of Congress - World Communist Movement: Selective Chronology 1818-1957. Vol. IV, 1954-55. Printed for House Committee on Un-American Activities (Box 274)
  - Charles J. Zinn. How Our Laws Are Made, D.C.: Government Printing Office, 1965 (Box 274)
  - Library of Congress - U.S. Foreign Aid: Its Purposes, Scope, Administration, and Related Information (Box 274)
    D.C.: U.S. Government Printing Office, 1959
  - Senate Document No. 86 - Prayers (Peter Marshall) during 80th & 81st Congress, 1947-49 (Box 274)
  - Committee on House Administration - History of the United States House of Representatives, D.C.: 1965 (Box 274)
  - Committee on Banking and Currency (House of Representatives) - Twenty Largest Stockholders on Record in ... Federal Reserve System, Oct. 1964 (Box 274)
  - Committee on Small Business (House of Representatives) Chairman's Report - Tax-Exempt Foundations and Charitable Trusts: Their Impact on Our Economy, Dec. 1962 (Box 274)
  - Committee on Small Business (House of Representatives) Sub-Committee Chairman's Report - Tax-Exempt Foundations and Charitable Trusts: Their Impact On Our Economy, Oct. 1963 (Box 274)
  - Tapes & Records
    - Phonograph recording, 1942 March 21, of Congressman Albert Gore's program with Smith as guest. 16 inch, 33 1/3 rpm - time 13'45", recorded in radio room of House of Representatives, P-410
    - Phonograph recording, 1942 July 29, of a radio talk by Smith, recorded at the radio room of the House Office Building. Two-16 inch, 33 1/3 rpm - time 29'40", P-411-412
    - Tape recording, 1960 October 4, an interview of Smith by Richard Rendell. One 7" reel - 12 minutes speed?, T-361
    - Tape recordings, 1961 June 13, of Smith speaking on "Is the Purpose, Federal Aid to Education or Federal Control of Education?". One 4" reel with what are presumed to be 3 duplicates (boxes do not list subject, but have same date written in same hand as identified copy). speed? length 6', T-362
    - Tape recording [March 1962] of the program, "Congress Calling" with Smith as speaker. One 5" reel, speed?, length ?, T-363
    - Phonograph record album, ca. 1963, "Viva la Alliance for Progress" containing lectures by Milton S. Eisenhower, Raúl Prebisch, José Figueres, Teodoro Moscosco, and Dean Rusk given under the auspices of the Johns Hopkins School of Advanced International Studies. six 12" 33 1/3 rpm records, P-413-418
    - Tape recording, n.d., "It's Your Business", presented by the National Association of Manufacturers and recorded by the American Broadcasting Corporation. One 7" reel, 7.5 ips, T-364
- Series XV: Scrapbooks
  - Scrapbooks, 1938-1940, 1
    of clippings and other materials re: Smith's campaign for Democratic nomination in the primary, 2) of clippings and other materials, 1939-1940 re: The Alien registration or "Smith Act", 3) materials, 1939 re: the Jefferson Memorial, and 4) clippings re: a milk investigation in the District of Columbia. 33 pages, black cloth cover loose-leaf
  - Scrapbook, 1943-44, 1955-58, 2
    clippings re: Smith and his Congressional career. 138 pages, green cloth cover.
  - Scrapbooks, (1957), 1958-1960, 3
    chiefly clippings re: Smith but a few photographs of Smith and his Congressional career. 72 pages green leatherette cover - some items laid in at end
  - Scrapbook, 1960-1961, 5
    clippings re: Smith and his Congressional career. 82 pages, brown leatherette cover, loose clippings laid in rear
  - Scrapbook, ca. 1960, 6
    of clippings re: Smith and the 86th Congress. 52 pages, green leatherette cover
  - Scrapbook, 1961-1962 (1963), 7
    clippings and some photographs re: Smith's Congressional career. 67 pages, brown leatherette cover
  - Scrapbook, 1963-1965, 8
    of clippings re: Smith and his Congressional career, 142 pages, green cloth cover.
  - Scrapbook, ca. 1965, 9
    clippings, photographs and cartoons re: Smith and his Congressional career. 52 pages, brown leatherette cover.
  - Scrapbook, 1965-1966, clippings, 10
    re: general subject, civil rights, and Judge Smith. 30 pages, red leatherette cover, some loose clippings in rear
  - Scrapbook, (1956) 1966, 11